Finding Aid for Michigan Daily Records, 1950-2006
Bentley Historical Library
- Negatives-Chronological, 1963-1980; 4.5 linear feet
  - 1977
    - July-December
      - Galens Day Collection, 12/02/1977 (Box 4)
      - Acufine Strike, 12/02/1977 (Box 4)
      - Hoon House File, 12/02/1977 (Box 4)
      - Gilbert and Sullivan Play "Patience", 12/06/1977 (Box 4)
      - Iran Students on Diag, 12/09/1977 (Box 4)
  - 1978
    - January-June
      - People Being Carded at Dooleys, 01/10/1978 (Box 4)
      - Ken Bloom at Ark, 01/06/1978 (Box 4)
      - Anti Planned Parenthood Picketers at Planned Parenthood Office, 01/20/1978 (Box 4)
      - Theater Class at Community High, 01/24/1978 (Box 4)
      - Grad and UGLi Lounges, 01/24/1978 (Box 4)
      - Community High, 01/24/1977 (Box 4)
      - Smoke Stoppers and Assist. Dean Community High, 01/24/1978 (Box 4)
      - Community High and Free Art, 01/24/1978 (Box 4)
      - 178 Senior Staff and Drupa(?) and Knox, 01/31/1978 (Box 4)
      - S. Africa Forum MLB Speaker, 01/31/1978 (Box 4)
      - S. Africa Protest, 01/31/1978 (Box 4)
      - V.A. Nurses, 02/02/1978 (Box 4)
      - ROTC Rifle Range, 02/03/1978 (Box 4)
      - ROTC Rifle Range, 02/03/1978 (Box 4)
      - Michigras, 02/04/1978 (Box 4)
      - 5th Ave. Bookstore, 02/10/1978 (Box 4)
      - Michigras, 02/10/1978 (Box 4)
      - Michigras at Union, 02/10/1978 (Box 4)
      - Nuclear Power #1, 02/12/1978 (Box 4)
      - Daily Business Staff, 02/15/1978 (Box 4)
      - Regents Meeting A Cuts, 02/16/1978 (Box 4)
      - Women's Conference, 02/16/1978 (Box 4)
        (Toole)
      - Regents Meeting, 02/16/1978 (Box 4)
      - Ypsi Council Candidates and Free Art, 02/16/1978 (Box 4)
      - Nuclear Power #2, 02/17/1978 (Box 4)
      - Amphibian Faculty and Father Hubbh(?), 02/21/1978 (Box 5)
      - Cinema (film lab), 02/22/1978 (Box 5)
        (Billinsky)
      - Seal Demonstration Detroit, 02/25/1978 (Box 5)
      - Clement Library, Igloo Tenant Demonstration, Law Quad Construction, 02/27/1978 (Box 5)
      - Anti-Nazi Protest and Big Puddle, 03/12/1978 (Box 5)
      - Dance School, 03/14/1978 (Box 5)
      - Dance School, 03/14/1978 (Box 5)
      - Staff Press Card Photos, 03/14/1978 (Box 5)
      - SA Protests and Regents, 03/16/1978 (Box 5)
      - SA Protests and Regents, 03/16/1978 (Box 5)
      - SA Protests Diag, 03/16/1978 (Box 5)
      - SA Protests and Regents, 03/16/1978 (Box 5)
      - Regents SA, 03/16/1978 (Box 5)
      - Hedy West at the Ark, 03/17/1978 (Box 5)
      - NOW Meeting, 03/18/1978 (Box 5)
      - Hooks NAACP, 03/20/1978 (Box 5)
      - Pretzel Bell Restaurant, 03/21/1978 (Box 5)
      - Council Debates Wheeler and Belcher, 03/23/1978 (Box 5)
      - Dance Marathon, 03/25/1978 (Box 5)
      - Bread and Butter Puppet Theater on Diag, 03/25/1978 (Box 5)
      - Belcher and Kenworthy Debate, 03/28/1978 (Box 5)
      - Wheeler Winning?, 04/03/1978 (Box 5)
      - Washtenaw County Jail, 04/05/1978 (Box 5)
      - Anti-Bakke Demonstration, 04/06/1978 (Box 5)
      - Special Olympics at Highpoint Center, 04/07/1978 (Box 5)
      - Legal Services Office Mich. Union, 04/07/1978 (Box 5)
      - U of M Recording and Sound Services, 04/07/1978 (Box 5)
      - Regents in Dearborn, 05/18/1917 (Box 5)
      - Cheese Shop (Kerrytown), 05/19/1993 (Box 5)
      - New Firehouse, 05/21/1978 (Box 5)
      - Senior Citizens' Rally at Island Park, 05/31/1978 (Box 5)
      - Freshman Orientation, 6/78 (Box 5)
      - GEO Hearings, 6/78 (Box 5)
      - Greek Festival, 06/01/1978 (Box 5)
      - Cobblestone Farms, 06/07/1978 (Box 5)
    - July-December
      - Art Fair Day 1, 7/78 (Box 5)
      - Art Fair Day 3, 7/78 (Box 5)
      - Old West Side Shot, 07/12/1978 (Box 5)
      - War Gaming Convention, 07/14/1978 (Box 5)
      - South African Press Conf., 07/16/1978 (Box 5)
      - Art Fair Set Up, 07/19/1978 (Box 5)
      - Art Fair Day 2, 07/20/1978 (Box 5)
      - Doubledecker Shuttle Bus, 07/25/1978 (Box 5)
      - Regents (Arnsen, Rose), 07/27/1978 (Box 5)
      - Pierce Primary Election Night, 08/08/1978 (Box 5)
      - Dill Ice Cream, 08/08/1978 (Box 5)
      - Hist. Dept. Chairman for Berket Blanchard service, 09/11/1978 (Box 5)
      - Free Art, Diag Preacher, Jade and Greg Trostad, 09/12/1978 (Box 5)
      - S.U.D.S. Protest, 09/13/1978 (Box 5)
      - Regent Bursley, 09/18/1978 (Box 5)
      - Legal Aid, 09/18/1978 (Box 5)
      - Frats Eating Ice Cream at Briarwood, 09/19/1978 (Box 5)
      - Art Fair #10, 09/30/1978 (Box 5)
        (Chang)
      - Browning & School Kids, 10/04/1978 (Box 5)
      - Norman and Nancy Blake, 10/04/1978 (Box 5)
      - Carl Levin, 10/06/1978 (Box 5)
      - "Map Man" James Miton, 10/06/1978 (Box 5)
      - ERA Game Artist, 10/12/1978 (Box 5)
      - South Africa, 10/13/1978 (Box 5)
      - Buchanon Interview, 10/14/1978 (Box 5)
        (Marks)
      - City Clerk "Happiness" Surprise and Thrift Shop, 10/17/1978 (Box 5)
      - Pollen Collector, 10/20/1978 (Box 5)
      - Mondale (1), 10/20/1978 (Box 5)
      - Veterans Meeting & Free Art, 10/21/1978 (Box 5)
      - Dooley's, 10/21/1978 (Box 5)
      - Vietnam Veterans Meeting, 10/21/1978 (Box 5)
      - Band Day Free Art, 10/21/1978 (Box 5)
      - Radio Racing, 10/24/1978 (Box 5)
      - Koka, S. African Speaker, 10/24/1978 (Box 5)
      - Proposal D Protest (Lansing), 10/26/1978 (Box 5)
      - Michigan Bandstand #1, 10/28/1978 (Box 5)
      - Michigan Bandstand #2, 10/28/1978 (Box 5)
      - Dancer, 11/03/1978 (Box 5)
      - Cobblestone Farm, 11/03/1978 (Box 5)
      - Rodney, Song Writer, 11/03/1978 (Box 5)
      - Leo Kottke, 11/05/1978 (Box 5)
      - Griffin and Milliken (1), 11/07/1978 (Box 5)
      - Griffin and Milliken (2), 11/07/1978 (Box 5)
      - Zhores Medvedev, 11/07/1978 (Box 5)
      - Election Night Ann Arbor Dems. Bullard, Pierce, 11/07/1978 (Box 5)
      - O'Malley, EX-MSA VP Smith, Latin Teach-In Lecture, 11/08/1978 (Box 5)
      - Free Art, 11/10/1978 (Box 5)
      - Project Community Site, 11/12/1978 (Box 5)
      - IM Football official, 11/14/1978 (Box 5)
      - Saco Taco, 11/14/1978 (Box 5)
      - "Wavey Gravey", 11/14/1978 (Box 5)
      - Prof. Werkopf, 11/14/1978 (Box 5)
      - Kate Rubin, 11/14/1978 (Box 5)
      - Peace Rally, Fleming's Last Speech, 11/20/1978 (Box 5)
      - Weight Lifter, 11/28/1978 (Box 5)
      - David Loui, Speaker on Asian Amer., 12/02/1978 (Box 5)
      - Women's B-Ball, Detroit, 12/02/1978 (Box 5)
      - Weisman-Klein & Free Art, 12/03/1978 (Box 5)
      - Tibet Monk/E.Q. Killer, 12/04/1978 (Box 5)
      - Grand Ole Opry Tryouts, 12/04/1978 (Box 5)
      - Ed Hood, 12/04/1978 (Box 5)
      - Jamie Kenworthy, 12/04/1978 (Box 5)
      - Schmuzzles, 12/04/1978 (Box 5)
      - Poverty, 12/06/1978 (Box 5)
      - David's Books, 12/06/1978 (Box 5)
      - AIF&EC "Fruit Brigade", 12/08/1978 (Box 5)
      - Robben Fleming "Farewell", 12/08/1978 (Box 5)
  - 1979
    - January-June
      - Art Fair, 1979 (Box 5)
      - Free Art, 01/05/1979 (Box 5)
      - LS&A Student Gov., 01/10/1979 (Box 5)
      - Downtown (2), 01/12/1979 (Box 5)
      - Wilmington, 02/10/1979; 01/13/1979 (Box 5)
      - Regents Meeting, 01/18/1979 (Box 5)
      - NASA Mural, 01/19/1979 (Box 5)
      - Ark, Lou Killey, 01/19/1979 (Box 5)
      - Earle & Free Art, 01/19/1979 (Box 5)
      - Roscoe Mitchell, 01/20/1979 (Box 5)
      - Hypnotist, 01/23/1979 (Box 5)
      - Israeli Prof./MSA A-Cuts, 01/24/1979 (Box 5)
      - Ruthi Navon, 01/24/1979 (Box 5)
        (Pitt)
      - Wilbur Cohen, 01/24/1979 (Box 5)
      - Libby's & Campbell's Strike, 01/25/1979 (Box 5)
      - Anxiety Program, 01/25/1979 (Box 5)
      - Ark, Mike Cooney, O'Neil, Hickerson, 01/26/1979 (Box 5)
      - Free Art & Lt. Richard Hill, 01/26/1979 (Box 5)
      - Botanical Gardens/New Daily Editors/Hugh Gilmore, 01/31/1979 (Box 5)
      - Press Passes #1, 2/79 (Box 5)
      - Press Passes #2, 2/79 (Box 5)
      - Press Passes #3, 2/79 (Box 5)
      - Press Passes 14, 2/79 (Box 5)
      - Ann Arbor Road Sign, 02/01/1979 (Box 5)
      - Dance Marathon, 02/03/1979 (Box 5)
        (Udelson)
      - Arbor Alliance Benefit at the Ark, 02/03/1979 (Box 5)
      - Frat Lottery for Florida, 02/02/1979 (Box 5)
      - Bullard, Soviet Satirist, 02/05/1979 (Box 5)
      - Melting Pot Discussion, 02/08/1979 (Box 5)
      - Edmund Muskie, 02/14/1979 (Box 5)
      - Stephen Withey, Dir. of Research Ctr. & Joggers, 2/9/79 (Box 5)
      - Rowing Practice, 02/12/1979 (Box 5)
      - Fair Person, 02/19/1979 (Box 5)
        (Oberdorfer)
      - City Hall & Steel Girders, 02/19/1979 (Box 5)
      - Kenworthy, 02/19/1979 (Box 5)
      - Mirage Dance, 02/20/1979 (Box 5)
        (Udialson)
      - The Ark, 02/22/1979 (Box 5)
      - Blacks on China Speaker, 02/23/1979 (Box 5)
      - Track Meet, Mike Cooney, 02/23/1979 (Box 5)
      - Solar Eclipse, 02/26/1979 (Box 5)
      - Detroit Jazz Stvs, 02/26/1979 (Box 5)
      - Syrian Refugee, "Mr. Albert", 02/28/1979 (Box 5)
      - Elaine Nobel, 02/28/1979 (Box 5)
      - Protest, 03/08/1979 (Box 5)
      - Gerald Ford Paper Place, 03/08/1979 (Box 5)
      - Ralley and Regents, 03/14/1979 (Box 5)
      - James Madison and constitution, 03/14/1979 (Box 5)
      - Public Comments, 03/14/1979 (Box 5)
      - Rally & Regents (S. Africa), 03/14/1979 (Box 5)
      - Speaker on Japanese Treatment During WWII, Kitano, 03/16/1979 (Box 5)
      - Gospel Concert, Fisk Singers, 03/17/1979 (Box 5)
      - St. Patrick's Day, 03/17/1979 (Box 5)
      - Free Art, 03/22/1979 (Box 5)
      - Al Haber, 1st Annual Grad. Library Party, 03/23/1979 (Box 5)
      - Wilma Rudolf, 03/23/1979 (Box 5)
      - Gargoyle, 03/28/1979 (Box 5)
      - Pac Candidates, 03/28/1979 (Box 5)
      - Sarah and Phil Power, 03/28/1979 (Box 5)
      - Joel Samaff, 03/30/1979 (Box 5)
      - Bus. Staff, 03/30/1979 (Box 5)
      - Levin-Kenworthy, 03/31/1979 (Box 5)
      - College Bowl Women's Day, Japanese Speaker, 03/31/1979 (Box 5)
      - Rackham Candidates, 03/31/1979 (Box 5)
      - MSA Votes Counted, 04/07/1979 (Box 5)
      - E.P. Women's-Right to Life, 04/07/1979 (Box 5)
      - RCYB, 04/10/1979 (Box 5)
      - E. Quad Media Stage Perf., 04/13/1979 (Box 5)
      - Publications series Logo, 04/13/1979 (Box 5)
      - Bicycle Cop, 06/01/1979 (Box 5)
    - July-December
      - Regents Meeting, Harold Shapiro new Pres., 07/27/1979 (Box 5)
        (Klausner)
      - Dead Head, 08/11/1979 (Box 5)
      - U. Cellar, 09/06/1979 (Box 5)
      - WCC Strike, 09/06/1979 (Box 5)
      - Gloria Steinem, 09/10/1979 (Box 5)
      - Admin., 09/11/1979 (Box 5)
      - ISR Building, 09/12/1979 (Box 5)
      - Eric & Todd, Cross Country cyclists, 09/12/1979 (Box 5)
      - Milliken, 09/12/1979 (Box 5)
      - Scalpers, 09/12/1979 (Box 5)
      - Prog., 09/14/1979 (Box 5)
      - Fans, 09/14/1979 (Box 5)
        (Seidler)
      - Houses, Ticket, Rick Leach's Helmet, Jersey at Barbers, Council Meeting Members, 09/17/1979 (Box 5)
      - Regents and Sorority, 09/21/1979 (Box 5)
      - Sorority and Free Art, 09/21/1979 (Box 5)
      - No Nukes! Ann Arbor Detroit Edison Protest, 09/28/1979 (Box 5)
      - Chem. Building Construction, 10/05/1979 (Box 5)
      - U. Cellar Contract Signing, 10/05/1979 (Box 5)
      - Trotter House, 10/05/1979 (Box 5)
      - Expo 1979/H.S. Underground Papers, 10/05/1979 (Box 5)
      - Bullard & Mich. Union Anniversary, 10/12/1979 (Box 5)
      - Lecture (Marroquin), 10/12/1979 (Box 5)
      - Ralph Nader, 10/19/1979 (Box 5)
      - Maggie Kuhn, Suck-Off Negs., 10/19/1979 (Box 5)
      - Student Production Rehearsal "In the Dark", 10/22/1979 (Box 5)
      - Car Slash, 10/26/1979 (Box 5)
      - Linwood Dunne, 11/03/1979 (Box 5)
      - Israel (Personal), 11/16/1979 (Box 5)
      - Mass. Senator Tsongas, 11/16/1979 (Box 5)
      - Kappa Kappa Gamma and GOP Ad in April 5 1973 Front Page, 12/03/1979, 1973-1979 (Box 5)
  - 1980
    - January-October
      - Gold Jewelry, 01/10/1980 (Box 5)
      - Hams Hall, 01/10/1980 (Box 5)
      - Folk Fest, 01/17/1980 (Box 5)
      - MSA Investment, 01/24/1980 (Box 5)
      - John Aristotle Phillips, 01/24/1980 (Box 5)
      - Dick Gregory, 01/24/1980 (Box 5)
      - Objectional Draft, 01/24/1980 (Box 5)
      - Allan Whiting, 01/24/1980 (Box 5)
      - Anti Registration Ralley and Space Invader Game, 01/30/1980 (Box 5)
      - JDL Speaker, 01/30/1980 (Box 5)
      - Regents Meeting, 02/14/1980 (Box 5)
      - Elephant, Donkey, 02/14/1980 (Box 5)
      - IPPS-Ed Gramlich/Business, 02/15/1980 (Box 5)
      - Kodak Cannister, Drummer and Rick Block, 03/27/1980 (Box 5)
      - Peace Accord Celebration, 03/27/1980 (Box 5)
      - Debby Gill, Co-Chairman Reagan-Bush Campaign Comm., 10/01/1980 (Box 5)
- Negatives-Topical, circa 1963-1980
  The Negatives-Topical, ca. 1963-1980 series is arranged alphabetically by subject. For the years 1976-1980, the researcher can use the Michigan Daily Index for assistance in determining the date of a given negative (the index is available on microfiche at the Bentley Historical Library).
  - Ann Arbor Sights (buildings, rural and street scenes) (Box 5)
  - Atlantic City (Box 5)
  - Concert Artists
    - B (Box 5)
    - C (Box 5)
    - D (Box 5)
    - E (Box 5)
    - F (Box 5)
    - G (Box 5)
    - H (Box 5)
    - I (Box 5)
    - J (Box 6)
    - L (Box 6)
    - M (Box 6)
    - N (Box 6)
    - O-P (Box 6)
    - R (Box 6)
    - S (Box 6)
    - T (Box 6)
    - U-Z (Box 6)
  - Construction (in and around Ann Arbor) (Box 6)
  - Detroit (Box 6)
  - Entertainment (Box 6)
    (mostly plays and festivals, but includes some concert shots)
  - Exhibits (mostly art) (Box 6)
  - Groups (Box 6)
  - Individuals (Box 6)
  - Meetings (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
  - Ohio (Box 7)
  - Outdoors (Box 7)
  - Plans (buildings and park) (Box 7)
  - Political Conventions (Box 7)
  - Protests (Box 7)
  - Quebec (Box 7)
  - Recreation (Box 7)
  - Regents (Box 7)
  - Sports: Mens
    - Baseball (Box 7)
    - Basketball
      - Undated, November 1966-January 19, 1978 (Box 7)
      - January 21, 1978-January, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Cross Country (Box 8)
    - Football
      - Undated (Box 8)
      - 1966 (Box 8)
      - 1967 (Box 8)
      - 1968 (Box 8)
      - 1969
        - Undated (Box 9)
        - April (Box 9)
        - September (Box 9)
        - October (Box 9)
        - November (Box 9)
      - 1970
        - Undated (Box 9)
        - March (Box 9)
        - August (Box 9)
        - September (Box 9)
        - October (Box 9)
        - November (Box 9)
      - 1971
        - Undated (Box 9)
        - March (Box 9)
        - September (Box 9)
        - October (Box 9)
      - 1972
        - Undated (Box 9)
        - March (Box 9)
        - November (Box 9)
      - 1973
        - Undated (Box 9)
        - September (Box 9)
        - November (Box 9)
      - 1974
        - September (Box 9)
        - October (Box 9)
        - November (Box 9)
      - 1975
        - Undated (Box 9)
        - April (Box 9)
        - September (Box 9)
        - October (Box 10)
        - November (Box 10)
      - 1976
        - Undated (Box 10)
        - January (Box 10)
        - September (Box 10)
        - October (Box 10)
        - November (Box 10)
        - December (award ceremony) (Box 10)
      - 1977
        - April (Box 10)
        - September (Box 10)
        - October (Box 10)
        - November (Box 10)
      - 1978
        - Undated (Box 10)
        - April (Box 10)
        - September (Box 10)
        - October (Box 10)
        - November (Box 10)
      - 1979
        - September (Box 10)
        - October (Box 10)
        - November (Box 10)
    - Golf (Box 10)
    - Gymnastics (Box 10)
    - Hockey
      - Undated-1975 (Box 10)
      - 1976-1980 (Box 11)
    - Horse Racing (Box 11)
    - LaCrosse (Box 11)
    - Racquetball (Box 11)
    - Rugby (Box 11)
    - Soccer (Box 11)
    - Swimming (Box 11)
    - Tennis (Box 11)
    - Track (Box 11)
    - Water Polo (Box 11)
    - Wrestling (Box 11)
  - Sports: Womens
    - Basketball (Box 11)
    - Gymnastics (Box 11)
    - Softball (Box 11)
    - Tennis (Box 11)
  - Toronto (Box 11)
  - University Campus (Box 11)
  - Ypsilanti (Box 11)
- Photographs and Contact Sheets, circa 1963-1980
  The Photographs and Contact Sheets series is comprised of five sub-series: Ann Arbor, Ypsilanti, Student Life, University, and Other, and within sub-series, alphabetically by topic. The majority of images are in the form of contact sheets.
  - Ann Arbor
    - Building Interiors (Box 12)
    - Churches and Clerics (Box 12)
    - Golf Courses (Box 12)
    - Humane Society (Box 12)
    - Kroger Boycott (Box 12)
    - Michigan Theater (Box 12)
    - Pretzel Bell (Box 12)
    - Rural Scenes (Box 12)
    - Second Chance (Box 12)
    - Street Scenes, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Ypsilanti
    - Town Scenes (Box 12)
  - Student Life
    - Campus Scenes
      - Diag, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Other, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - College Association for Research of Principles (CARP) (Box 12)
    - Classroom Scenes (Box 12)
    - Dancing (Box 12)
    - Demonstrations/Protests
      - General (Box 12)
      - Antiwar (Box 12)
      - Gay Rights (Box 12)
      - "Halt Assault" March (Box 12)
      - Human Rights (Box 12)
      - Iranian Hostages (Box 12)
      - Nuclear Power (Box 12)
      - South Africa (Box 12)
      - Women's Studies (Box 12)
    - Entertainers, 4 folders (Box 12)
    - ERA Volunteer (Box 12)
    - Graduation (Box 12)
    - Hash Bash (Box 12)
    - Hazing (Box 12)
    - International Center (Box 12)
    - Jazz (Box 12)
    - Largon, Mary Ann (Box 12)
    - Meetings (Box 12)
    - Michigan Band (Box 12)
    - Moot Court (Box 12)
    - Peace Corps (20th Anniversary) (Box 12)
    - Plays (Box 12)
    - Physical Therapy (Box 12)
    - Recreation (Box 12)
    - Registration (Box 12)
    - Sculptures (Box 12)
    - Skeleton (Box 12)
    - Skunk (Box 12)
    - Social Events (Box 12)
    - Speakers
      - Anderson, John (Box 12)
      - Ferency, Zolton (Box 12)
      - Ford, Gerald, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Gregory, Dick (Box 12)
      - Nader, Ralph (Box 12)
      - Vitale, Dick (Box 12)
      - Others (Box 12)
    - Sports
      - Baseball (Box 12)
      - Basketball, 4 folders (Box 12)
      - Field Hockey (Box 12)
      - Football
        - Undated, 8 folders (Box 12)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 12)
        - 1977, 3 folders (Box 12)
        - 1978, 3 folders (Box 12)
        - 1979, 3 folders (Box 12)
      - Gymnastics (Box 12)
      - Hockey (Box 12)
      - Softball (Box 12)
      - Swimming (Synchronized) (Box 12)
      - Tennis (Box 12)
      - Track (Box 12)
      - Volleyball (Box 12)
      - Wrestling (Box 12)
    - Student Government Council (Box 12)
    - Student Groups, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Trotter House (Box 12)
    - WCBN (radio broadcasting) (Box 12)
  - University
    - Buildings
      - General (Box 12)
      - Power Center Dedication (Box 12)
      - Student Activities Building (Box 12)
    - Personnel (faculty, staff, regents) (Box 12)
    - Schools and Departments (Box 12)
  - Other
    - Labor Unions (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Individuals, 6 folders (Box 13)
      - Other (Box 13)
    - Police (Box 13)
    - Political Campaigns (Box 13)
    - Republican National Convention, 1980; 3 folders (Box 13)
    - State and Federal Government (includes Jimmy Carter and Ronald Reagan), 2 folders (Box 13)
- Faculty, Staff, Administrators-Biographical Files, 5 linear feet
  Faculty, Staff, Administrators Biographical Files series is arranged alphabetically by surname and include the name of the department(s) in which the person worked. Materials in the Biographical files range from clippings and news releases to curricula vitae.
  - A-B
    - Adams, Adelaide Alice -- Fine Arts, History of Art (Box 14)
    - Adams, Julian -- Biology (Box 14)
    - Adamson, Thomas C., Jr. -- Engineering (Box 14)
    - Adelson, Joseph B. -- Psychology (Box 14)
    - Aga-Oglu, Mrs. Kamar -- Museums (Box 14)
    - Albano, Joseph F. -- Arch. & Design (Box 14)
    - Alexander, Richard D. -- Zoology (Box 14)
    - Allen, John M. -- Zoology (Box 14)
    - Allen, Richard John -- Pediatrics (Box 14)
    - Allen, Sally -- Biology (Box 14)
    - Allison, Alexander W. -- English (Box 14)
    - Allmand, Charles M. -- Personnel, U-Hospital (Box 14)
    - Alvord, Herbert H. -- Engineering (Box 14)
    - Anderson, Leigh -- Chemistry (Box 14)
    - Anderson, Lester -- Education (Box 14)
    - Anderson, Ronald -- Education (Box 14)
    - Anderson, William R. -- Botany (Box 14)
    - Angell, Robert -- Sociology (Box 14)
    - Applegate, Oliver C. -- Dentistry (Box 14)
    - Arnold, Chester -- Biology, Geology (Box 14)
    - Arpaci, Vedat S. -- Mech. Engineering (Box 14)
    - Arthos, John -- English (Box 14)
    - Aseltine, Lyle F. -- Dentistry (Box 14)
    - Atkinson, John W. -- Psychology (Box 14)
    - Avery, James K. -- Dentistry (Box 14)
    - Axelrod, Solomon J. -- Public Health, -- Economics (Box 14)
    - Bader, Arno L. -- English (Box 14)
    - Badgley, Carl E. -- Surgery (Box 14)
    - Bagchi, Basu K. -- Psychiatry (Box 14)
    - Baic, Dusan -- Experimental Biology (Box 14)
    - Bailey, Reeve M. -- Zoology (Box 14)
    - Baird, Claribel -- Speech (Box 14)
    - Baker, Burton L. -- Anatomy (Box 14)
    - Baker, Dean C. -- Journalism (Box 14)
    - Baker, Robert -- Slavic Languages (Box 14)
    - Baker, Sheridan W., Jr. -- English (Box 14)
    - Ballis, William B. -- Political Science (Box 14)
    - Balzhiser, Richard E. -- Chemical Engineering (Box 14)
    - Banfield, Ralph W. -- Naval Science (Box 14)
    - Barker, H. Kenneth -- Bureau of Appts (Box 14)
    - Barlow, Robin -- Economics (Box 14)
    - Baromeo, Chase -- Music (Box 14)
    - Barrows, Herbert C., Jr. -- English (Box 14)
    - Bates, Marston -- Zoology (Box 14)
    - Bauer, Jere Marklee -- Internal Medicine (Box 14)
    - Beach, Lowell W. -- Education (Box 14)
    - Bean, John W. -- Physiology (Box 14)
    - Beardsley, Richard K. -- Anthropology (Box 14)
    - Beck, Charles B. -- Botany (Box 14)
    - Beckett, Morley B. -- Public Health (Box 14)
    - Behrman, Samuel J. -- Medicine (Box 14)
    - Beierwaltes, William H. -- Medicine (Box 14)
    - Bender, Leonard F. -- Medicine (Box 14)
    - Bender, Robert A. -- Gene Research (Box 14)
    - Benedict, Milbry "Moby" -- Baseball (Box 14)
    - Benford, Harry B. -- Engineering (Box 14)
    - Benninghoff, William S. -- Botany (Box 14)
    - Berg, Elliot -- Economics (Box 14)
    - Bernstein, Isadore A. -- Biological Chemistry (Box 14)
    - Berry, Ralph M. -- Civil Engineering (Box 14)
    - Berry, William T. -- Music School (Box 14)
    - Bett, Virgil M. -- Business Admin (Box 14)
    - Beyer, Robert E. -- Biology (Box 14)
    - Bhattacharya, Mihir -- Finance (Box 14)
    - Bidlack, Russell E. -- Library Science (Box 14)
    - Binder, Henry -- English (Box 14)
    - Bishop, Ronald C. -- Medicine (Box 14)
    - Bishop, William W., Jr. -- Law (Box 14)
    - Blatt, Josef -- Music (Box 14)
    - Block, Walter D. -- Biological Chemistry (Box 14)
    - Bloomer, H. Harlan -- Speech (Box 14)
    - Blume, William W. -- Law (Box 14)
    - Blumenthal, Michael W. -- Honors, Economy of U.S (Box 14)
    - Bollinger, Lee -- Law (Box 14)
    - Bohr, David F. -- Physiology (Box 14)
    - Bolt, Jay A. -- Mech. Engineering (Box 14)
    - Bonk, Wallace J. -- Library Science (Box 14)
    - Borchardt, J.A. -- Engineering (Box 14)
    - Bordin, Edward -- Psychology (Box 14)
    - Bornstein, George -- English (Box 14)
    - Bornstein, Morris -- Economics (Box 14)
    - Bossart, R. Eugene -- Music (Box 14)
    - Boston, Orlan W. -- Mech. Engineering (Box 14)
    - Bowditch, John III -- History (Box 14)
    - Bowman, Robert A. -- Public Health (Box 14)
    - Boyce, Ernest -- Civil Engineering (Box 14)
    - Boys, Richard C. -- English (Box 14)
    - Brandt, Carl G. -- English (Box 14)